

Profile

Passionate brand marketer with 6+ years of experience working with multiple national brands. Dedicated to finding/using creative and traditional marketing techniques to connect brands with consumers not only on a product level but on a emotional level as well. With the end goal of pushing brand presence further than previously imagined while simultaneously connecting consumers with products that meet their needs.

Employment History

Manager Stoker's Brand, Turning Point Brands

APRIL 2021 - PRESENT

- Plan and execute yearly marketing plan for smokeless brands
- Design and execute POS, advertising campaigns, product packaging, and digital marketing efforts for all Smokeless Products
- Lead consumer promotions and retail smokeless promotions
- Manage, design, and execute all international smokeless brands
- People management (Agency and internal team members)
- Budget Management (2.6 million budget responsibility)
- Management of all marketing data analytics
- Coupon Program Management

Associate Brand Manager - Smokeless, National Tobacco Company (Turning Point Brands)

JANUARY 2019 - MARCH 2021

- Design and execute POS, advertising campaigns, product packaging, and digital marketing efforts
- Lead Consumer Promotions
- Lead Consumer Sampling Events
- Assist in new product development
- Assist in development of marketing strategy for multiple company brands
- Create and manage marketing analytics
- Manage/Design/Execute all International Smokeless Brands

Marketing Assistant - Smokeless Brands, National Tobacco Company (Turning Point Brands)

MAY 2015 - DECEMBER 2018

- Assist in development of marketing strategy for multiple company brands
- Design and execute POS, advertising campaigns, product packaging, and digital marketing efforts
- Support field sales effort with marketing programs and materials
- Create and manage marketing analytics

Education

Master of Business Administration, University of Louisville

AUGUST 2017 - AUGUST 2018

Bachelor of Science - Marketing, University of Louisville

1312 Etawah Avenue Louisville, 40222 United States 502-475-1439

Maxgerdes517@gmail.com

Links

Details

Linkedin

Skills

Leadership

Microsoft Excel

Teamwork

Communication

Adaptability

Time Management Skills

Excellent Communication Skills

Multitasking Skills

Microsoft Office

Brand Management

Corporate Entrepreneur

Graduated with a BS in marketing and a double minor in Entrepreneurship/Management.